at the colony two weeks have passed the
chicks are testing their independence
and spending time away from their
mothers all that is except
one as the last to hatch he's way behind
in
development while the older chicks are
boisterous and confident he still feels
most comfortable in his mother's
pouch but penguins are sociable birds
and to survive he must learn to play his
part in The
Colony it's a daunting
Prospect but the little chick finds some
courage
[Music]
it's a shaky
start but he mustn't lose his nerve
time for a bit of tough
love with every step he gains more
[Music]
confidence it's just as well he has so
many friends to make
[Music]
but when you're the
smallest it's tough to join the
[Music]
gang for now there's always mom
out in the open ocean the fathers are
reving in being back in the
[Music]
water they haven't eaten for four whole
months and have lost half their body
[Music]
weight to stock up on fish and Squid
they hold their breath for up to 20
minutes and dive to nearly 600 M deeper
than any other
[Music]
[Applause]
bird at the colony 3 weeks have passed
and the chick is confidently following
his mother wherever she
goes he's still learning how things
should be done
[Applause]
and how they
shouldn't he soon thinks there's nothing
left to
[Music]
learn so nervous toddler turns cocky
Explorer but at this age she mustn't let
him out of her sight
[Music]
w